<ModOps>
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">    
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414018244</GUID>
      <Text>HUMILIATION</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414018245</GUID>
      <Text>RESTORATION</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414006637</GUID>
      <Text>Royal Convoy Escort</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414018044</GUID>
      <Text>A larger marketplace with a tall market tower suitable for large settlements.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1442800</GUID>
      <Text>City Market</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414018045</GUID>
      <Text>Central City</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414018172</GUID>
      <Text>Bring [AssetData(5380) Text] to your storages in Horai</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414018173</GUID>
      <Text>Bring [AssetData(133097) Text] to your storages in Horai</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414018174</GUID>
      <Text>Bring [AssetData(118728) Text] to your storages in Horai</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414018175</GUID>
      <Text>Bring [AssetData(112694) Text] to your storages in Horai</Text>
    </Text>
    <!-- 3rdparty Fluffs when clicking island buildings -->
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414018121</GUID><!-- Goodwill Lost shipment text -->
      <Text>[AssetData([NotificationContext CharacterGUID]) Text] is very disappointed about you losing out on this shipment and adjusts your future payment rate.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414006695</GUID>
      <Text>This airship looks like a good vessel for any unexpected last-minute escape, which is something a smuggler always needs to be ready for. So there it lies, patiently waiting for its future time to shine.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414006696</GUID>
      <Text>The paperwork done in this office used to look fairly different. Now that most of the former E.T.A. possessions are under the direct control of the crown, the effort has shifted to cover black market trading.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414006697</GUID>
      <Text>While built twenty-odd years ago as an administrative wing, the rooms now make for an exceptionally good prison. For what does a smuggling business need these many prisoners, you say? Nevertheless, there are an obscene number of new faces on each visit.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414015072</GUID>
      <Text>Hongyipao</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414015071</GUID>
      <Text>Junk Shipyard</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414015061</GUID>
      <Text>Officials House</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414040615</GUID>
      <Text>Admiral Wu Guowei's Lighthouse</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414018130</GUID>
      <Text>By the time of Admiral Wu's great-grandfather's campaign to recover the Eye of the Dragon more than a century ago, the Tianming Empire fielded junks to great effect. While their construction has not changed much since, times have — rendering the once-very capable vessels obsolete — yet now the Tianming Empire is neither capable nor allowed to procure modern ships.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414018131</GUID>
      <Text>At the verge of total ruination, the Tianming Empire is solely held together by two things: military force and religion. At sites like these the people of Majipun, like many other citizens of the East pray for a way out of this century of humiliation.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414018132</GUID>
      <Text>Strolling through the garden, viewers encounter a series of carefully composed scenes, each crafted with deliberate grace. In times of existential crisis, the Ruize Emperor finds solace in maintaining these gardens in immaculate condition at a great personal expense — one of the few powers he still holds onto with certainty.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414018133</GUID>
      <Text>Tianming soldiers nicknamed these weapons the "Red Barbarian Cannon," a nod to the La Corona invaders from whom the first models were captured. Though later refined, they remain relics of a bygone era — a time when the Tianming Empire stood as a formidable military power.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414018160</GUID>
      <Text>The central administrative yamen not only serves as the Admiral's headquarters from which he administers a strict military rule over Majipun, but also marks a place where the Ruize Emperor's control over the Tianming Guo is still untouched.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414018161</GUID>
      <Text>The local population of Majipun works on these farms to feed themselves with rice and tea. This is all they need, at least according to Admiral Wu.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414015077</GUID>
      <Text>Administrator's Palace</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>  <!-- Geb and Nut are James Goodwill's pets. -->
      <GUID>1414015089</GUID>
      <Text>Geb's Hut</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414015090</GUID>
      <Text>Nut's Hut</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414015091</GUID>
      <Text>Duduk</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414018176</GUID>
      <Text>This majestic pagoda, built centuries ago, rises at the summit of a great staircase that ascends through the Arch of Hope toward divinity. Towering high above the earthly concerns of ordinary life, it stands as a bridge between the mortal world and the sacred.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414015084</GUID>
      <Text>Great Pigeon Pagoda</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414018177</GUID>
      <Text>The workers of Omega Haven look towards the central clocktower, often just to find that their shift hasn't yet ended.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414015085</GUID>
      <Text>Clocktower</Text>
    </Text>
    <!-- Item -->
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414011052</GUID>
      <Text>Librarian of Zelos</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414006736</GUID>
      <Text>Reading everything he can get his bookwormy hands on, he draws only the most fascinating and convoluted conclusions. Once he discovered that houses can have basements...</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1440508</GUID>
      <Text>[AssetData(1999005351) Text]</Text>
    </Text>
    <!-- Foreign Trading Company Texts (NH specific)-->
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414018030</GUID>
      <Text>Provides surrounding Magnate Businesses with [AssetData(1999005351) Text], increasing their output.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414018031</GUID>
      <Text>Distributes [AssetData(1999005351) Text] to surrounding Magnate Businesses.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414018032</GUID>
      <Text>A harbor to build Magnate Businesses around and import goods from across the world.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414018046</GUID>
      <Text>Generates [AssetData(1999005351) Text]</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414018047</GUID>
      <Text>For every unit consumed, [AssetData(1999005351) Text] are added to the island storage.</Text>
    </Text>
    <!-- Zoo -->    
    <Text>
      <GUID>14443035</GUID>
      <Text>Horaiese Food &amp; Drink Production</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414017000</GUID>
      <Text>PLANET OF THE APES</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414017002</GUID>
      <Text>BAMBOO FOREST</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414017003</GUID>
      <Text>OCEANIA</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414006829</GUID>      <!-- Oceania - ItemSet - Description -->
      <Text>Beyond the Wallace Line, the animals of Oceania beckon with their unusual primeval forms.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414006830</GUID>      <!-- Bamboo Forest SETBUFF - TownhallBuff - Description -->
      <Text>Learning that patience is the wisdom of the wild, and seeing the tranquil energy of these animals have allowed your citizenry to take life more slowly and savor each sip, as even tea tastes deeper in stillness.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414006831</GUID>      <!-- Planet of the Apes SETBUFF - TownhallBuff - Description -->
      <Text>The antics of these simian cousins have allowed your citizenry to reflect upon themselves and become more careful. </Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414006833</GUID>      <!-- Oceania SETBUFF - TownhallBuff - Description -->
      <Text>These strange and exotic beasts have tempered the appetite of your citizenry, granting them the art of mindful eating and the stomach of an island sage.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414006834</GUID>      <!-- Planet of the Apes - Itemset - Description -->
      <Text>Apes together strong. Retvrn to monkee, am I right?</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414017004</GUID>
      <Text>Red Panda</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414017005</GUID>
      <Text>Panda Bear</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414017006</GUID>
      <Text>Koala</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414017007</GUID>
      <Text>Macaque Ape</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414017008</GUID>
      <Text>Sharkwhale</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414017009</GUID>
      <Text>Wallace Flying Frog</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414017010</GUID>
      <Text>Reticulated Python</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414017011</GUID>
      <Text>Komodo Dragon</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414017012</GUID>
      <Text>Eared Seal</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414017013</GUID>
      <Text>Pangolin</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414017014</GUID>
      <Text>Amur Leopard</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414006737</GUID>
      <Text>&lt;b&gt;Rhacophorus nigropalmatus.&lt;/b&gt; Living amongst the steamy, sunlit canopies of Sunda, this curious little frog cannot actually fly, but it sure can try.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414017018</GUID>
      <Text>Weasel Enclosure</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414006738</GUID>
      <Text>&lt;b&gt;Mustela altaica.&lt;/b&gt; Does not actually live in the great mountains of Hindun but in the lush bamboo forests in the surrounding foothills. It's a myth that it plans its own cities when nobody is looking.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414006739</GUID>
      <Text>&lt;b&gt;Ailuropoda melanoleuca.&lt;/b&gt; A cute, cute, and most importantly cute black-and-white bear that sits around and eats bamboo all day, lest it dies of starvation if it misses a meal.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414006740</GUID>
      <Text>&lt;b&gt;Varanus komodoensis.&lt;/b&gt; This enormous lizard from Sunda is no fire-spitting dragon, but a very venomous and very dangerous reptile nonetheless.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414006741</GUID>
      <Text>&lt;b&gt;Malayopython reticulatus.&lt;/b&gt; the longest snake ever known to humankind. It strikes not with venom, but by wrapping its massive coils around its prey and strangling it with silent precision.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414006742</GUID>
      <Text>&lt;b&gt;Macaca fuscata.&lt;/b&gt; A small, red-faced monkey from the islands north of Horai. Clever and mischievous by nature, it is a quick learner, an avid hot spring enthusiast, and endlessly playful.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414006743</GUID>
      <Text>&lt;b&gt;Manis pentadacty.&lt;/b&gt; Treasured by the inhabitants of the Tianming Empire for its supposedly healing scales, this silent, timid creature feeds itself at night on a diet of termites and ants.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414018225</GUID>
      <Text>&lt;b&gt;Ailurus fulgens&lt;/b&gt; A charming flame-colored animal that shares little in common with the big pandas beyond its name and the fact that it also eats bamboo all day. With its masked face, ringed tail, and feline grace, it leads a crepuscular, arboreal life high in the trees.</Text>
    </Text>
	<Text>
      <GUID>1414018226</GUID>
      <Text>&lt;b&gt;Arctocephalus galapagoensis&lt;/b&gt; A seal living on the many islands north of Ulimaroa that loves warm weather and basking in the sun.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414018227</GUID>
      <Text>&lt;b&gt;Phascolarctos cinereus&lt;/b&gt; A curious little critter that spends most of its time on eucalyptus trees. In fact, they're so locked in that they can't even recognize a lifestyle outside of their beloved trees.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414018228</GUID>
      <Text>&lt;b&gt;Rhincodon typus&lt;/b&gt; Is it a whale? Is it a shark? It's... both? Inhabiting the southern tropical seas peacefully feeding on krill and plankton, only the smallest specimen can fit into a zoo.</Text>
    </Text>
    <!-- Wonder Buff Texts -->    
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414018178</GUID>
      <Text>Productivity Buff</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414018179</GUID>
      <Text>Residence Buff</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414018180</GUID>
      <Text>Residences in Street Distance are supplied with [AssetData(1440405) Text].</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414018181</GUID>
      <Text>Bonus Buff</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414018182</GUID>
      <Text>Affects in Street Distance:</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414187028</GUID>
      <Text>[Selection Object Factory PostboxResidents] Residents in Radius</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414018183</GUID>
      <Text>Residents gain bonus happiness from [ItemAssetData(1414187031) InputBenefitAllAdditionalHappinessFormatted].</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414018184</GUID>
      <Text>Unique Buff</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414018185</GUID>
      <Text>Affects [ItemAssetData(1414187030) ItemOrBuffEffectTargetsFormatted] in Street Distance</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414018186</GUID>
      <Text>Affects [ItemAssetData(1414187033) ItemOrBuffEffectTargetsFormatted] on island</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414018187</GUID>
      <Text>Affects on island:</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414018188</GUID>
      <Text>Defense Buff</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414018189</GUID>
      <Text>Affects [ItemAssetData(1414187034) ItemOrBuffEffectTargetsFormatted] on island</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414018190</GUID>
      <Text>Affects [ItemAssetData(1414187036) ItemOrBuffEffectTargetsFormatted] in Street Distance</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414018191</GUID>
      <Text>Residences with the [ItemAssetData(1414187039) AllSubstituteNeedsFormatted] need fulfilled, are provided with [ItemAssetData(1414187039) AllProvidedNeedsFormatted].</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text><!-- Gen 3rdParty Feedback to Wonder built -->
      <GUID>1414006694</GUID>
      <Text>[AssetData([NotificationContext CharacterGUID]) Text] is delighted by the Wonder.</Text>
    </Text>
    <!-- Botanical Garden Buff Texts -->
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414018210</GUID>
      <Text>Activates [AssetData(1414007001) Text] if built in Horai</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414018211</GUID>
      <Text>Activates [AssetData(1414007002) Text] if built in Horai</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414018212</GUID>
      <Text>Activates [AssetData(1414007003) Text] if built in Horai</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414018213</GUID>
      <Text>Activates [AssetData(1414007007) Text] if built in Horai</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414018214</GUID>
      <Text>Activates [AssetData(1414007010) Text] if built in Horai</Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
</ModOps>