<ModOps>
    <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414019037</GUID>
            <Text>[AssetData([NotificationContext CharacterGUID]) Text] offers you some rice for pickup to get you through the monsoon.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414019038</GUID>
            <Text>Monsoons regularly sweep across these lands, shutting down all farm production for their duration. Your towns haven't really been set up well for this. To get you through your first Monsoon, James Goodwill rushes to help.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414019039</GUID>
            <Text>[AssetData([NotificationContext CharacterGUID]) Text] asks if you're ready to load the rice.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414019040</GUID>
            <Text>[AssetData([NotificationContext CharacterGUID]) Text] hands you the rice.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414019041</GUID>
            <Text>[AssetData([NotificationContext CharacterGUID]) Text] is surprised that you don't even want the rice.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414019042</GUID>
            <Text>[AssetData([NotificationContext CharacterGUID]) Text] offers you guidance on Horai.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414019043</GUID>
            <Text>[AssetData([NotificationContext CharacterGUID]) Text] is happy you are prepared for the next monsoon.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414019044</GUID>
            <Text>[AssetData([NotificationContext CharacterGUID]) Text] notes your lackluster preparation and will not bail you out.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414019045</GUID>
            <Text>Monsoons are harsh, they stop all your production. The next monsoon is only a matter of time, so start preparing!</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414019046</GUID>
            <Text>Your farms will stop producing during the Monsoon. During the Dry Season, your farms can harvest, and they get a 50% production boost - so two rice farms are still enough for one sushi factory. Your task: provide enough warehouse space to store it for the monsoon time.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414019047</GUID>
            <Text>Have in Storage: &lt;br/&gt;[Conditions QuestCondition CurrentAmount]/[Conditions QuestCondition Amount]t [AssetData([Conditions QuestCondition Context]) Text]</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414040617</GUID>
            <Text>Tutorial - If at first you don't succeed...</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414040620</GUID>
            <Text>Tutorial - Seasons</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414018000</GUID>
            <Text>Construct a shopping street around your world's fair on [Area Area([Conditions QuestArea]) CityName], consisting of:</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414040434</GUID>
            <Text>E.T.A. Delivery: Gallery of Glamour</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414040436</GUID>
            <Text>E.T.A. Delivery: Gallery of Glamour</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414040437</GUID>
            <Text>E.T.A. Delivery: Gallery of Glamour</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414040439</GUID>
            <Text>E.T.A. Delivery: Gallery of Glamour</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414018001</GUID>
            <Text>Deliver 15t of any Luxury product to the shopkeeper at your world's fair on [Area Area([Conditions QuestArea]) CityName].</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414018002</GUID>
            <Text>Dealer Childan is happily expecting your display items.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414018003</GUID>
            <Text>Dealer Childan thanks you for the display items.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414018004</GUID>
            <Text>Start any World's Fair Event on [Area Area([Conditions QuestArea]) CityName]</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414018005</GUID>
            <Text>A splendid day! I’ve been chosen to host this season’s grand World’s Fair Shopping Arcade. Oh... oh...., excuse me, in which reality have I left my manners? Allow me to introduce myself. I am Robert Childan, purveyor of fine antiquities and rare luxuries. I dream of a grand campus of craftsmanship, a true showcase of the best-of-the-best. You don't happen to have luxuries in quantity around? No matter—we've much to do. Let’s begin building this campus together.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414018006</GUID>
            <Text>Exquisite pieces! True works of art, delicately crafted. Everything is ready — except... where are the visitors? Has the event not even started yet? We need to begin preparations, tout suite!</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414018007</GUID>
            <Text>Someone just arrived and immediately bought out our entire stock — no questions asked! Now that’s what I call a total success.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414018008</GUID>
            <Text>Dealer Childan eagerly awaits you at the world's fair</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414018009</GUID>
            <Text>Select your World's Fair</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414018010</GUID>
            <Text>Dealer Childan requests some samples for display.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414018011</GUID>
            <Text>Dealer Childan is interested in what happened to the requested samples.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414018012</GUID>
            <Text>Send your Blockade Runners overseas to [Area Area([Conditions QuestArea]) CityName], so you are ready when a buyer shows up.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414018013</GUID>
            <Text>Dealer Childan unveils his pavilion of luxury goods to deep-pocketed investors, eager to spend without blinking.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414018014</GUID>
            <Text>[AssetData([NotificationContext CharacterGUID]) Text] wants to attract potential buyers at a World's Fair.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414018015</GUID>
            <Text>What better way to move large volumes of contraband — legally, of course — than under the glamorous lights of the World’s Fair? Sales are brisk, and demand often outweighs supply... but not this time. James Goodwill has secured the services of a seasoned antiquities dealer to manage the operation, ensuring nothing slips through the cracks — except, perhaps, a few ethics.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414018016</GUID>
            <Text>Build a Gate, Pavilion, and Tower in a 20-tile radius around your World's Fair.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414018017</GUID>
            <Text>Obtain World's Fair Ornaments by completing architectural exhibitions.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414018018</GUID>
            <Text>Robert "Bob" Childan deals with antiquities first and foremost, a category of good that isn't produced in the necessary quantities for an event of this size. For the best shopping experience, Mr. Childan needs more samples to exhibit in his showroom.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414018019</GUID>
            <Text>The showroom is complete, now the only thing missing is the customers. Organizing a big event like this should be a one-day-job at maximum — at least when asking Mr. Childan.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414018020</GUID>
            <Text>Select your world's fair to begin preparations for an exhibition. Currently-running exhibitions do not count.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414018021</GUID>
            <Text>Someone just bought our entire stock, including shipping service. Mr. Childan is happy about the booming success in sales, never even asking himself where all the luxuries came from.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414018022</GUID>
            <Text>[AssetData([NotificationContext CharacterGUID]) Text] is happy about the sudden appearance of a buyer.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414018023</GUID>
            <Text>Volkhetka Voyage</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414018024</GUID>
            <Text>In order to provide a market, the volunteer units must first make their voyage across the sea.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414019001</GUID>
            <Text>Sinking Ship</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414019002</GUID>
            <Text>A loud, shrill wheeze jolts your crew from their afternoon rest, sending them into a panic. At first, it sounds like the boiler taking on water — a sure sign that the ship is sinking fast, and that disaster is only moments away.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414019003</GUID>
            <Text>Abandon Ship!</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414019009</GUID>
            <Text>!EventPool Kamchatka</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414019004</GUID>
            <Text>Rescue the sailors</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414019005</GUID>
            <Text>Calm the crew down</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414019006</GUID>
            <Text>Have a technician examine the situation</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414019008</GUID>
            <Text>Chaos erupts as your crew loses all sense of order, leaping into the sea without waiting for the lifeboats to be lowered. But quickly, it becomes clear they’ve made a grave mistake. There’s no apparent leak, and sailors rushing to the engine room find no signs of water flooding the ship.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414019010</GUID>
            <Text>In a stroke of luck, you manage to save most of your crew. Despite some serious injuries, they’ll recover. But not all are so fortunate — a young sailor lies nearly lifeless on the deck.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414019011</GUID>
            <Text>You manage to save most of your crew, although some of your crew is lost.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414019012</GUID>
            <Text>The rescue efforts quickly end in disaster. Among the drowning sailors, you spot some of your volunteer recruits in the water, fighting for their lives.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414019013</GUID>
            <Text>Try to reanimate the young sailor</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414019014</GUID>
            <Text>The young sailor fights for his life alongside your crew. Too young to be at the end of his journey, he reemerges in the realm of the living, sparking hope for a full recovery.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414019015</GUID>
            <Text>The reanimation efforts prove in vain as the young sailor succumbs to his injuries on the deck. The crew stands helpless, staring at the lifeless body. The sight of such a young soul slipping away, so soon after losing other crewmates, is almost too much for them to bear.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414019016</GUID>
            <Text>Hide the sailor from the rest of the crew</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414019017</GUID>
            <Text>The young sailor quietly succumbs to his injuries alone, in the darkness. A personal tragedy, one that your crew remains unaware of, believing the sailor perished in the waters — a reality they had already come to terms with hours ago.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414019018</GUID>
            <Text>For now, the crew is rallying behind your leadership, setting their panic aside and entrusting you to be right on the issue. But this leaves you with a difficult decision: What comes next? A troubling noise emanates from the engine room, hinting at a potential leak and the possibility that the boilers are taking on water.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414019019</GUID>
            <Text>Go to the engine room</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414019020</GUID>
            <Text>Try to find the leak on the hull</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414019021</GUID>
            <Text>Your words fail to convince, and chaos quickly erupts. The crew, in a panic, abandons all reason, leaping into the sea without waiting for the lifeboats to be lowered. But quickly, it becomes clear they’ve made a grave mistake. There’s no apparent leak, and sailors rushing to the engine room find no signs of water flooding the ship.</Text>
            <!-- Roughly the same as 1414019008 -->
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414019022</GUID>
            <Text>The crew is completely confident in the machinist’s strong leadership, trusting him to be right on this matter. But this leaves you with a difficult decision: What comes next? A troubling noise emanates from the engine room, hinting at a potential leak and the possibility that the boilers are taking on water.</Text>
            <!-- Roughly the same as 1414019018 -->
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414019023</GUID>
            <Text>And there it is — the source of all this chaos. The ship isn't sinking fast, nor is it sinking at all. What appeared to be a boiler room flooding with water is actually just a damaged steam pipe, cracked open like an egg, leaking steam in all directions. Rerouting the steam through the adjacent pipe seems like a viable solution — assuming, of course, you have some technical expertise.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414019024</GUID>
            <Text>Repair the damaged pipe</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414019025</GUID>
            <Text>Have the machinist fix the pipe</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414019026</GUID>
            <Text>Mute the pipe with Cloth</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414019027</GUID>
            <Text>The pipe is swiftly repaired by your crew's skilled hands. The loud clanging noise ceases as the steam now flows smoothly through the adjacent pipe. With a satisfied nod, the crew declares the mission a success and heads for the deck, leaving behind a few meters of scrap metal — useful for future repairs — in your hands.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414019028</GUID>
            <Text>Whatever your technicians are attempting, nothing seems to be working. Steam continues to escape through unexpected openings, and the damaged pipe remains stubbornly intact. At least the noise has been reduced, making the sound easier to bear for the time being, though an annoyance is evident on your crew's faces.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414019029</GUID>
            <Text>Slapping cloth onto the problem doesn’t seem to help. The steam forces the fabric away from the pipe, and no amount of screws can hold it in place when the cloth simply rips apart. The sharp remnants of the broken pipe don’t make things any easier, slicing through the cloth and leaving you with a constant racket and an annoyed crew for the rest of the journey.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414019030</GUID>
            <Text>With a deafening bang, your inexperienced repairmen pay the price for their hubris. Having forgotten to shut down the machines for these repairs, the adjacent pipe violently ruptures, sending fragments flying in all directions. Your technician never stood a chance. To add insult to injury, the explosion only worsens the noise, transforming into a full-blown cacophony.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414019031</GUID>
            <Text>Slapping cloth over the problem will have to suffice for the remainder of the trip. The fabric seems to hold, and the noise is muffled to a level where undisturbed sleep is once again possible. Steam escapes through cleverly cut vents, and the clattering parts are now buffered by thick layers of cloth. It’s not a perfect solution, but the damaged pipe is no longer a pressing issue.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414019032</GUID>
            <Text>The long voyage of your squadron has borne fruit. A significant influx of recruits from the New World will provide the necessary manpower for the uprising to turn the tide of the conflict. Now, all that remains is to secure the weapons needed for the final push toward freedom.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414019032</GUID>
            <Text>!RewardKamchatka</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414019033</GUID>
            <Text>The diver emerges from the depths, having survived the tumultuous waves. He confirms that there is no leak in the ship, and the mysterious noise must have another source. While the crew is reassured, their curiosity remains unsatisfied, and they are eager to uncover the true origin of the sound.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414019034</GUID>
            <Text>Try to find a leak from the inside</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414019048</GUID>
            <Text>Frustration grows quickly among the crew as the search effort becomes increasingly chaotic. In a moment of tension, the first officer snaps and abandons ship, sparking pandemonium. The crew, in a panic, abandons all reason, leaping into the sea without waiting for the lifeboats to be lowered. But quickly, it becomes clear they’ve made a grave mistake. The rough seas prove even more perilous than the supposed threat, and from the water, the officers realize the ship isn’t sinking after all.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414019049</GUID>
            <Text>The search for the leak proves fruitless, and though it’s a relief, it also leaves you with lingering concerns. On the one hand, it’s good news that no leak was found, confirming the ship’s safety. On the other hand, the mystery of the deafening noise from the engine room remains unresolved.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414019050</GUID>
            <Text>The Island of Wild Animals</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414019051</GUID>
            <Text>Land Ahoy! After weeks of sailing, the ship finally reaches a large island, devoid of human settlement. What does catch the eye, however, are the many rare and wild animals scattered across the land. Your crew is keen to capture a few to bring home as exotic pets.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414019052</GUID>
            <Text>Allow your crew to sail to the island</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414019053</GUID>
            <Text>Forbid your crew to visit the island</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414019054</GUID>
            <Text>Euphoric cheers erupt from your crew as the ship nears the island. Sailors scramble to gather whatever tools they can find—nets, spades, ropes — anything that might help them catch a wild companion. As boots hit the sand, they turn to you eagerly, awaiting your command on the best way to wrangle exotic pets from the wilderness.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414019055</GUID>
            <Text>After the hardships of the past week, the prospect of rare and unique pets had the crew in high spirits. But now, with the island shrinking behind you on the horizon, it’s clear that dampening their excitement hasn't exactly helped the general mood aboard the ship.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414019056</GUID>
            <Text>Go Hunting with Lassos</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414019057</GUID>
            <Text>Construct Traps for the Animals</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414019058</GUID>
            <Text>Sit down and Pray for Animals to show up</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414019062</GUID>
            <Text>Have your Animal Whisperer catch an Animal</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414019059</GUID>
            <Text>That was easy! You catch a wild animal off guard — before it even realizes what’s happening, it’s already tangled in your lasso. One of your sailors now has a new companion! Shall they try for more?</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414019060</GUID>
            <Text>The nimble creatures seem to evade your hunting efforts — each attempt foiled by their quick reflexes and keen senses. But with enough patience, even luck can falter. One unfortunate beast is caught off guard by the hunters — and is captured. Now that they've had a taste of success, how should they continue the hunt?</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414019061</GUID>
            <Text>No matter their size, the animals remain too clever and agile for your hunters to catch. Their efforts border on the ridiculous — more a slapstick comedy than a hunt — as they begin accidentally capturing fellow sailors instead. Perhaps it’s time to reconsider your approach?</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414019063</GUID>
            <Text>The well-set trap snaps into action. Inside, your crew finds an unexpected prize: a new pet for the ship. With care, the sailors carry it aboard. The first catch is in — how should the hunt continue?</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414019064</GUID>
            <Text>The trap is far from ideal — barely concealed and crudely made. But sometimes, all it takes is one particularly unfortunate or foolish animal. With a sudden loud snap, the trap closes, producing a bewildered new pet inside. What’s the next move?</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414019065</GUID>
            <Text>What a waste of effort this trap has turned out to be. While it accomplishes being visible from far away — with the bait inexplicably placed outside rather than within. It has failed to catch animals, a fact your crew grows increasingly aware of as they wait in vain. Eventually, their interest in the trap fades entirely.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414019067</GUID>
            <Text>Hallelujah! It seems fate has indeed moved in your favor — a particularly bold creature wanders straight into the arms of one of your sailors, who quickly befriends it. Just like that, a new pet joins your crew. How should your sailors go on?</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414019068</GUID>
            <Text>In the end, patience prevails. A curious animal manages to entangle itself in a nearby bush, and your sailors help free it. Grateful — or perhaps simply confused — the creature now finds itself part of the crew.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414019069</GUID>
            <Text>Literal thoughts and prayers, however, have proven insufficient. What were your sailors even thinking?</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414019070</GUID>
            <Text>Leave the island</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414019071</GUID>
            <Text>And with that — the hunt is over. Your volunteers pack up their equipment, ready to set sail once more for their next destination. Alongside them are a motley crew of animals, turning what was once a formidable ship into something closer to a floating zoo.</Text>
        </Text>

        <Text>
            <GUID>1414018034</GUID>
            <Text>In the rugged Volkhetka Peninsula, a rebellion against the tyrannical local government is rapidly losing momentum. The flame of resistance flickers, weakened not by lack of will, but by the absence of trained fighters. Though driven by a fierce desire for freedom, the rebels lack the experience to carry their cause forward, risking failure — and leaving the people to endure oppression. James Goodwill urges immediate action: to send vital aid and skilled fighters to support the rebels before their movement collapses entirely.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414040701</GUID>
            <Text>Volunteer Fighters</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414018035</GUID>
            <Text>Send the Fighters overseas by completing the "Volkhetka Voyage" expedition</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414040700</GUID>
            <Text>E.T.A. Delivery: Volkhetka Voyage</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414018036</GUID>
            <Text>Recruit in the New World:&lt;br/&gt;[AssetData([Conditions QuestCondition Context]) Text] [Conditions QuestCondition CurrentAmount]/[Conditions QuestCondition Amount]</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414018037</GUID>
            <Text>!StoryTextAlcohol01</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414018038</GUID>
            <Text>Keep average productivity in every [AssetData([Conditions QuestCondition Context]) Text] above:&lt;br /&gt;[Conditions QuestCondition CurrentAmount]% / [Conditions QuestCondition Amount]%</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414018039</GUID>
            <Text>[AssetData([NotificationContext CharacterGUID]) Text] is happy that a big producer of alcohol can quickly step in for the lost storage.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414018040</GUID>
            <Text>Deliver an Umeshu sample to the Umeshu tasters</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414018041</GUID>
            <Text>[AssetData([NotificationContext CharacterGUID]) Text] is very happy that you could help him out with a shipment of Alcohol.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414018042</GUID>
            <Text>[AssetData([NotificationContext CharacterGUID]) Text] discovers that someone contaminated his Alcohol Storages.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414018043</GUID>
            <Text>[AssetData([NotificationContext CharacterGUID]) Text] likes your local umeshu and would be very happy to buy some Alcohol from you.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414041300</GUID>
            <Text>Flowers for the Wife</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414041301</GUID>
            <Text>Any Lotus Flower</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414041302</GUID>
            <Text>It is the Gōngrén's wedding anniversary day, and he is trying to create a very special gift to his beloved.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414041303</GUID>
            <Text>I would like to give my wife a special gift for our wedding anniversary. May I ask for your generous help in finding a Lotus flower for her?</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414041307</GUID>
            <Text>Deliver to [AssetData(1446101) Text] at your harbor: [AssetData([Conditions QuestCondition DeliveryObject(ObjectiveIndex)]) Text]</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414041801</GUID>
            <Text>The workers at your sake brewery have learned of atole, and their curiosity is piqued. They propose that exploring the beverages of distant lands could inspire new techniques — and perhaps elevate their own craft.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414041802</GUID>
            <Text>I recently heard of a curious drink from the New World — they brew it from local grains, much like how we brew sake from rice. If you could bring back a sample for us, we would be most grateful. Who knows — there might even be something useful we can learn from it.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414041803</GUID>
            <Text>Our gratitude for entertaining our request. The atole tasted like nothing that I expected — what a joy to discover something new!</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414041800</GUID>
            <Text>Atoll Atole</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414041700</GUID>
            <Text>Double Agent</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414041701</GUID>
            <Text>Admiral Wu knows all too well that his Empire’s technology has long lagged behind. If the dynasty ever hopes to stand against the powers of the Old West, he must uncover the secrets of their naval innovations. Will you become his double agent?</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414041702</GUID>
            <Text>I know you command an impressive fleet, and I’d like to see your latest additions. If you could just provide me with some photos of those ships... purely for admiration.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414041703</GUID>
            <Text>These vessels look impressive. Now, if you're willing, perhaps you could sell me a few for a new fleet. I assure you — they won’t see action on any battlefield... at least, not one involving you. </Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414042000</GUID>
            <Text>The Dreamer - Traveling Faraway</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414042001</GUID>
            <Text>A young local Gōngrén has heard tales of the distant landscapes of the Old World. Imagination stirred, they now seek to witness these wonders for themselves, and has requested your help.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414042002</GUID>
            <Text>I’ve heard that your hometown is host to many magnificent structures. I know someone who would like to see pictures of them, if that's all right?</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414042004</GUID>
            <Text>It’s a great city, and he’s eager to visit himself. However, his uncle, Admiral Wu, will likely disapprove of the idea. Perhaps you could arrange for him to be smuggled to your hometown through that contact of yours?"</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414042005</GUID>
            <Text>Journey to the West</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414042006</GUID>
            <Text>Admiral Wu's nephew, who is on his way to the Old World.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414042007</GUID>
            <Text>Young Dreamer's letter</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414042008</GUID>
            <Text>A letter from Admiral Wu's nephew to his uncle, explaining his reasons for going to the Old World.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414042009</GUID>
            <Text>[AssetData([NotificationContext CharacterGUID]) Text] is furious about his nephew and wants to catch him.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414042010</GUID>
            <Text>Pick up:&lt;br/&gt;Admirals nephew at your harbour</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414042011</GUID>
            <Text>Bring the Admiral's nephew to James Goodwill</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414042012</GUID>
            <Text>Thank you for everything. I am now able to journey to the Old World aboard Mr. Goodwill's ship. I am sorry to say that I have very little money left, but please, if you would, deliver this letter to my uncle. I am certain he will understand and be willing to repay you on my behalf.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414042013</GUID>
            <Text>Deliver:&lt;br/&gt;[Conditions QuestCondition Amount(ObjectiveIndex)] [AssetData([Conditions QuestCondition DeliveryObject(ObjectiveIndex)]) Text] to Majipun.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414042014</GUID>
            <Text>It seems his reasons are valid, and I wish that all will be well in his journey to the Old World. These gifts come from my nephew, and while honor obliges me to present them to you, do not mistake them for a gesture of my personal affection! When you learned of my nephew's decision to embark on such a distant journey, protocol would have called for consulting me first!</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414042015</GUID>
            <Text>Furiously, the Admiral opens the letter.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414042016</GUID>
            <Text>[AssetData([NotificationContext CharacterGUID]) Text] wants to know whether you are ready to bring the Admiral's nephew to Goodwill's island.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414042017</GUID>
            <Text>[AssetData([NotificationContext CharacterGUID]) Text] asks if the Admiral's nephew wants to come aboard his ship.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414042019</GUID>
            <Text>[AssetData([NotificationContext CharacterGUID]) Text] triumphantly captures his nephew.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414042020</GUID>
            <Text>Dear Uncle:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I trust you will understand that I am not leaving without saying farewell, and that my journey to the West is not a mere whim for adventure.  &lt;br /&gt;Rather, I believe it presents an opportunity to make a name for myself in that faraway land and bring honor to our family name — Suen.&lt;br /&gt;I am aware of the dangers in this voyage, so I hope you will not inform my parents of my journey for the time being. Should anything happen to me, I hope you will care for my mother — your sister — and my younger brother, Deming. If I reach my destination safely, I will ensure that someone returns with a letter at the first opportunity.&lt;br /&gt;Additionally, please do not let my friend be burdened by any trouble on my behalf. They only offered their help at my request, and I would be grateful if you could offer them a token of appreciation on my behalf.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Yours respectfully,&lt;br /&gt;Dezhang</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414042100</GUID>
            <Text>Journey to the West - Accomplished Success</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414042101</GUID>
            <Text>A magnate from Horai seeks your audience, wishing to share with you the joy of his recent success. Will you spare a moment to hear his story?</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414042102</GUID>
            <Text>Good evening, my friend! I wouldn't be here without your help. Thanks to you, my fortunes have multiplied, and I've made a fine profit trading in exotic goods. Now that success has found me, please, accept these gifts — a token of my gratitude.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414042103</GUID>
            <Text>Listen, my friend — my trading fleet just uncovered a smuggling operation backed by La Corona! Come, let’s seize this opportunity together and get them all! We’ll both profit handsomely… and who knows? We may even earn a medal or two!</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414042106</GUID>
            <Text>I hear your Queen has sent an envoy to honor your efforts against smuggling! But he seems to have gotten lost on his way. Go find him!</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414042107</GUID>
            <Text>Find the Queen's envoy, who has gotten lost in your city</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414042109</GUID>
            <Text>[AssetData([NotificationContext CharacterGUID]) Text] hands you his gift.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414041600</GUID>
            <Text>Fighting Fire With Fire</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414041602</GUID>
            <Text>Mr. Goodwill seems to be in urgent need of warships to fend off the rising Pyrphorian threat. But with neither Admiral Wu nor the Crown willing to provide support, there's only one option left — and congratulations, you've just landed yourself a sole-sourced procurement contract.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414041601</GUID>
            <Text>The Pyrphorians are getting more and more aggressive! Our recent losses are starting to jeopardize business contracts, and I find myself in dire need of new warships. If you could sell me some... I would compensate you generously.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414041603</GUID>
            <Text>Sell to Mr. Goodwill: [Conditions QuestCondition CurrentAmount]/[Conditions QuestCondition Amount] Monitors</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414041604</GUID>
            <Text>Sell the requested ships at the Quest Givers harbor.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414041605</GUID>
            <Text>[AssetData([NotificationContext CharacterGUID]) Text] offers you a Ship sale quest.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414042110</GUID>
            <Text>The Dreamer - Returning Home</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414042111</GUID>
            <Text>An old Magnate acquaintance from Horai has found you, looking preoccupied and forlorn. Do you have time to see him?</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414042112</GUID>
            <Text>My friend, lately I’ve been dreaming of my hometown night after night, and a deep homesickness has taken root in my heart. Please, if you can, bring me some fish from Horai. A taste of home might be just what I need.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414042113</GUID>
            <Text>The stomach is often the most homesick of all organs... no matter where I travel, it's the familiar tastes that whisper of home. I've prepared everything — but my sons have wandered off! Please, help me find them. They’re running around somewhere nearby. Tell them it’s time to return — to our true home.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414042114</GUID>
            <Text>The Old Magnate's son</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414042115</GUID>
            <Text>Find the Old Magnate's sons in your city: [Conditions QuestCondition CurrentAmount]/[Conditions QuestCondition Amount]</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414042116</GUID>
            <Text>Thank you for all these years. We're finally heading home. I've placed the belongings I can't take with me into a trust — they’re now in your care.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414042117</GUID>
            <Text>Magnate's Ship</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414042118</GUID>
            <Text>Goodbye, my friend. When I return, I will build a home as magnificent and modern as this place. One day, my posterities will no longer need to leave home to chase success — they’ll find it in their homeland.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414042119</GUID>
            <Text>Autobiography of the Prodigal Immigrant</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414042120</GUID>
            <Text>The tale of a self-made entrepreneur from the Far East who rises to fame and fortune in the West, only to return to his hometown years later. Some say it mirrors the author’s own life, while others insist it’s purely a work of fiction.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414042121</GUID>
            <Text>Select your Magnate friend's ship to bid him a final farewell.</Text>
        </Text>
    </ModOp>
</ModOps>