<ModOps>
    <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
        
    <Text>
        <GUID>1414018050</GUID>
        <Text>+30% Productivity for Gold, Brass and Steel Furnaces</Text>
      </Text>
      <Text>
        <GUID>1414008550</GUID>
        <Text>Workload Deregulation Act</Text>
      </Text>
      <Text>
        <GUID>1414018051</GUID>
        <Text>-20% Workforce needed for Lightbulb, Gramophone and Jewellry Workshops</Text>
      </Text>
      <Text>
        <GUID>1414008551</GUID>
        <Text>Freemasonry</Text>
      </Text>
      <Text>
        <GUID>1414018052</GUID>
        <Text>+1 Item Slot for all Harbourmaster's Offices</Text>
      </Text>
      <Text>
        <GUID>1414008552</GUID>
        <Text>Harbour Stewardship Act</Text>
      </Text>
      <Text>
        <GUID>1414008553</GUID>
        <Text>Multilateral Free Trade Act</Text>
      </Text>
      <Text>
        <GUID>1414018053</GUID>
        <Text>+50% Import Speed for Import Piers</Text>
      </Text>
      <Text>
        <GUID>14443044</GUID>
        <Text>Import Piers</Text>
      </Text>
      <Text>
        <GUID>1414008554</GUID>
        <Text>Crop Stockpiling Act</Text>
      </Text>
      <Text>
        <GUID>1414018054</GUID>
        <Text>+25 Tons of Storage for Crop Storages and Depots</Text>
      </Text>
      <Text>
        <GUID>1414018163</GUID>
        <Text>The [AssetData([NotificationContext CharacterGUID]) Text] was attacked and stained by pigeons in an all-out attack!</Text>
      </Text>
      <Text>
        <GUID>1414018164</GUID>
        <Text>The [AssetData([NotificationContext CharacterGUID]) Text] now wants you to catch the perpetrators of such insolence.</Text>
      </Text>
      <Text>
        <GUID>1414018165</GUID>
        <Text>A Magnate was attacked by a wild pigeon and now his spectacle maker charges him for the cleaning job. That sounds like a situation where the taxpayer should step in, obviously.</Text>
      </Text>
      <Text>
        <GUID>1414018166</GUID>
        <Text>The [AssetData([NotificationContext CharacterGUID]) Text] asks you to pay the cleaning fee at his local spectacle maker.</Text>
      </Text>
      <Text>
        <GUID>1414040619</GUID>
        <Text>Pigeon on the Attack</Text>
      </Text>
      <Text>
        <GUID>1414018167</GUID>
        <Text>Catch the Pigeon which stained the Magnate's glasses.</Text>
      </Text>
      <Text>
        <GUID>1414018168</GUID>
        <Text>Pay the 5 Coin cleaning fee for the Magnate's glasses.</Text>
      </Text>
      <Text>
        <GUID>1414018171</GUID>
        <Text>Produces goods.</Text>
      </Text>
      <Text>
        <GUID>1414019073</GUID>
        <Text>Towards New Horizons</Text>
      </Text>
      <Text>
        <GUID>1414019074</GUID>
        <Text>Towards New Horizons</Text>
      </Text>
      <Text>
        <GUID>1414019075</GUID>
        <Text>Following the signing of the treaty of equality, the Queen has started a concessionary settlement program in the borderlands of Horai. Sail to the Region to claim your lands.</Text>
      </Text>
      <Text>
        <GUID>1414006017</GUID>
        <Text>Do not underestimate passive trade. When playing with every trader, you will be able to obtain all farm and intermediate goods from all regions that way.</Text>
      </Text>
      <Text>
        <GUID>1414187049</GUID>
        <Text>Tooth of Buddha</Text>
      </Text>
      <Text>
        <GUID>1414187050</GUID>
        <Text>Encased in gold and crystal, the Buddha Tooth Relic radiates serene reverence, a timeless symbol of enlightenment and devotion.</Text>
      </Text>
      <Text>
        <GUID>1414187051</GUID>
        <Text>Jingu Bang</Text>
      </Text>
      <Text>
        <GUID>1414187052</GUID>
        <Text>Forged in the heart of the sea and bound by magic, Sun Wukong’s staff shifts in size at will, a weapon of chaos wielded by the Monkey King himself.</Text>
      </Text>
      <Text>
        <GUID>1414187053</GUID>
        <Text>Baiju Rake</Text>
      </Text>
      <Text>
        <GUID>1414187054</GUID>
        <Text>Wrought from celestial iron and tipped with nine cruel prongs, the Baiju Rake strikes with the weight of heaven and the stubborn force of the earth.</Text>
      </Text>
      <Text>
        <GUID>1414187055</GUID>
        <Text>Ritual Seal</Text>
      </Text>
      <Text>
        <GUID>1414187056</GUID>
        <Text>Carved in stone and steeped in authority, the seal leaves behind more than a mark — it imprints identity, power, and the quiet weight of tradition.</Text>
      </Text>
      <Text>
        <GUID>1414187057</GUID>
        <Text>Treasure Sword</Text>
      </Text>
      <Text>
        <GUID>1414187058</GUID>
        <Text>Tempered by flame and spirit, the treasure sword gleams with ancestral pride, a blade that cuts not just flesh but fate itself.</Text>
      </Text>
      <Text>
        <GUID>1414187059</GUID>
        <Text>Ritual Incense</Text>
      </Text>
      <Text>
        <GUID>1414187060</GUID>
        <Text>Spiraling skyward in fragrant wisps, ritual incense weaves the unseen bridge between the mortal and the divine.</Text>
      </Text>
      <Text>
        <GUID>1414005072</GUID>
        <Text>1 Stupa Relic</Text>
      </Text>
      <Text>
        <GUID>1414018222</GUID>
        <Text>An original relic for the Stupa Wonder</Text>
      </Text>
      <Text>
        <GUID>1414018300</GUID>
        <Text>Must be in Range of [AssetData(1441330) Text]</Text>
      </Text>
      <Text>
        <GUID>1414018301</GUID>
        <Text>Company Production</Text>
      </Text>
      <Text>
        <GUID>1414018302</GUID>
        <Text>All Company Productions</Text>
      </Text>
      <Text>
        <GUID>1414018303</GUID>
        <Text>Farms cannot harvest anything during the monsoon season. All Farm Modules are automatically paused. Wait for the Dry Season to start harvesting crops again.</Text>
      </Text>
      <Text>
        <GUID>1414040223</GUID>
        <Text>Abandoned Ruins are being excavated...</Text>
      </Text>
      <Text>
        <GUID>1414011006</GUID>
        <Text>Crop-Gathering Backpack</Text>
      </Text>
      <Text>
        <GUID>1414011007</GUID>
        <Text>This straw backpack can be filled with as much crops as one's back can support.</Text>
      </Text>
      <Text>
        <GUID>1414011008</GUID>
        <Text>Gifted Chopsticks</Text>
      </Text>
      <Text>
        <GUID>1414011009</GUID>
        <Text>Special chopsticks gifted by Admiral Wu's mother.</Text>
      </Text>
      <Text>
        <GUID>1414011010</GUID>
        <Text>Tea Box</Text>
      </Text>
      <Text>
        <GUID>1414011011</GUID>
        <Text>A special box to keep tea leaves fresh for the best tea for that special occasion.</Text>
      </Text>
      <Text>
        <GUID>1414011012</GUID>
        <Text>Umeshu Jar</Text>
      </Text>
      <Text>
        <GUID>1414011106</GUID>
        <Text>A cheap jar to keep Umeshu always on hand.</Text>
      </Text>
      <Text>
        <GUID>1414011107</GUID>
        <Text>Lacquered Meal Box</Text>
      </Text>
      <Text>
        <GUID>1414011108</GUID>
        <Text>A beautifully crafted container, its glossy surface shimmering with intricate designs, perfect for serving a meal in elegance.</Text>
      </Text>
      <Text>
        <GUID>1414011109</GUID>
        <Text>Go Board</Text>
      </Text>
      <Text>
        <GUID>1414011110</GUID>
        <Text>"On an emotionless grid, empires rise and fall with the placement of a single stone.</Text>
      </Text>
      <Text>
        <GUID>1414011111</GUID>
        <Text>Gourd Bottle</Text>
      </Text>
      <Text>
        <GUID>1414011112</GUID>
        <Text>Despite its humble inspiration, this is the finest porcelain one may have ever seen.</Text>
      </Text>
      <Text>
        <GUID>1414011113</GUID>
        <Text>Sake Bowl</Text>
      </Text>
      <Text>
        <GUID>1414011114</GUID>
        <Text>Sipping sake from the delicate lip of this ceramic bowl, one can't but reflect on fleeting moments and forgotten toasts.</Text>
      </Text>
      <Text>
        <GUID>1414011115</GUID>
        <Text>Bento Lunch Box</Text>
      </Text>
      <Text>
        <GUID>1414011116</GUID>
        <Text>Neatly packed, carefully prepared — a small menagerie of flavors in a wooden box.</Text>
      </Text>
      <Text>
        <GUID>1414011117</GUID>
        <Text>Rabbit Incense</Text>
      </Text>
      <Text>
        <GUID>1414011118</GUID>
        <Text>A cute ceramic vessel for incense. Guaranteed to calm your nerves—unless you're a carrot.</Text>
      </Text>
      <Text>
        <GUID>1414011119</GUID>
        <Text>Neko Sculpture</Text>
      </Text>
      <Text>
        <GUID>1414011124</GUID>
        <Text>A mischevious kitty, pawing the air to draw prospective shoppers into its grasp.</Text>
      </Text>
      <Text>
        <GUID>1414011125</GUID>
        <Text>Bonsai</Text>
      </Text>
      <Text>
        <GUID>1414011126</GUID>
        <Text>A living poem in miniature — patience shaped in leaves and bark.</Text>
      </Text>
      <Text>
        <GUID>1414011127</GUID>
        <Text>Manga</Text>
      </Text>
      <Text>
        <GUID>1414011128</GUID>
        <Text>Some books are not for everyone.</Text>
      </Text>
      <Text>
        <GUID>1414011129</GUID>
        <Text>Onsen Bucket</Text>
      </Text>
      <Text>
        <GUID>1414011130</GUID>
        <Text>Simple, wooden, and warm to the touch — bringing the onsen into your own home.</Text>
      </Text>
      <Text>
        <GUID>1414011131</GUID>
        <Text>Pagoda Construction Plans</Text>
      </Text>
      <Text>
        <GUID>1414011132</GUID>
        <Text>Sanctuary Construction Plans</Text>
      </Text>
      <Text>
        <GUID>1414011133</GUID>
        <Text>Royal Palace Construction Plans</Text>
      </Text>
      <Text>
        <GUID>1414011134</GUID>
        <Text>Buddha Construction Plans</Text>
      </Text>
      <Text>
        <GUID>1414011135</GUID>
        <Text>Prince Tower Construction Plans</Text>
      </Text>
      <Text>
        <GUID>1414011136</GUID>
        <Text>Stupa Construction Plans</Text>
      </Text>
      <Text>
        <GUID>1414011137</GUID>
        <Text>Sparrow Netsuke Button Prototype</Text>
      </Text>
      <Text>
        <GUID>1414011138</GUID>
        <Text>Even simple ceramics can be jewellery. This clever prototype shows this off, and could even and make others jealous of one's fine couture.</Text>
      </Text>
      <Text>
        <GUID>1414005073</GUID>
        <Text>Monument Plans</Text>
      </Text> 
      <Text>
        <GUID>1414018304</GUID>
        <Text>The Foreign Trading Company can support Company Production in Horai wihin its radius, which grows with the Population on your island.</Text>
      </Text>    
      <Text>
        <GUID>1414018305</GUID>
        <Text>Expand your Storage for Trade Licenses by building a Foreign Trading Company Warehouse. If you don't have any yet, you can fulfill Magnate Needs, conduct delivery missions at my island or build Export Docks at the Foreign Trading Company in the Old World.</Text>
      </Text>    
      <Text>
        <GUID>1414018306</GUID>
        <Text>And if you then still have Trade Licenses to spare, you can use them to import new resources from the World Markets. As far as I know, there is no Tungsten to be found in your territories yet, but you can still get your hands on that resource. You know, it makes for exceptional lightbulb filament - and that's only one of your options!</Text>
      </Text>       
      <Text>
        <GUID>1414018307</GUID>
        <Text>If you have Trade Licenses, you might want to build Regional Offices to increase output of nearby Company Production.</Text>
      </Text>      
      <Text>
        <GUID>1414018308</GUID>
        <Text>Your Magnates can generate Trade Licenses, and they are pretty productive at that! Per ton of consumed Radios, Blue Cheese, Silk vests and Fountain Pens consumed, a Trade License is added to your storage. Use them in your Foreign Trading Company, or ship them to Horai to supply your Regional Offices with Trade Licenses.</Text>
      </Text>    
      <Text>
        <GUID>1414018309</GUID>
        <Text>Variation</Text>
      </Text>      
      <Text>
        <GUID>1414018310</GUID>
        <Text>Alternative look for this building.</Text>
      </Text>  
      <Text>
        <GUID>1414018311</GUID>
        <Text>Alternative Skin</Text>
      </Text>  
      <Text>
        <GUID>1414018312</GUID>
        <Text>Longevity Crown Replica</Text>
      </Text>  
      <Text>
        <GUID>1414018313</GUID>
        <Text>It fools the fool's eye, but a replica crown remains a replica crown. An original relic might be a better choice.</Text>
      </Text>
      <Text>
        <GUID>1414006752</GUID>
        <Text>The wandering workers seek a better future for themselves in your city.</Text>
      </Text>
      <Text>
        <GUID>1414006749</GUID>
        <Text>The wandering workers unwillingly move on, hoping to find their luck elsewhere.</Text>
      </Text>
      <Text>
        <GUID>1414006750</GUID>
        <Text>The wandering workers are delighted by the warm welcome to your city.</Text>
      </Text>
      <Text>
        <GUID>1414006751</GUID>
        <Text>The Tianming Guo is nothing more than a hell on earth; misery, hunger, and banditry are everywhere! We will forever be at your service, if you would be so gracious as to let us into your city...</Text>
      </Text>
      <Text>
        <GUID>1414006762</GUID>
        <Text>The small settlement, home to the working staff of Omega Haven, sees its inhabitants come together day by day for the morning mass in this mysterious chapel.</Text>
      </Text>
      <Text>
        <GUID>1414006763</GUID>
        <Text>[AssetData([NotificationContext CharacterGUID]) Text] supports your decision to not take in the workers.</Text>
      </Text>
      <Text>
        <GUID>1414006764</GUID>
        <Text>[AssetData([NotificationContext CharacterGUID]) Text] despises your draining of the Tianming Empire's workforce.</Text>
      </Text>
      <Text>
        <GUID>1414006765</GUID>
        <Text>[AssetData([NotificationContext CharacterGUID]) Text] condemns your colonialist expansion in Horai.</Text>
      </Text>
      <Text>
        <GUID>1414006766</GUID>
        <Text>Majipun was once a thriving trade port on the Horaiese borderlands, a symbol of promise under the Tiangming Empire’s Golden Age. But after the Tianming Empire’s defeat at the hands of the West, those ambitions collapsed. Now positioned directly on the frontlines, it has been placed under military administration by Admiral Wu and repurposed as a naval base. Stripped of the optimism of earlier years, its residents face a fading horizon — many now see departure as their only future.</Text>
      </Text>
      <Text>
        <GUID>1414006767</GUID>
        <Text>The Admiral has evidence on crimes of some immigrant workers and issued an arrest warrant. Finding and returning the wanted criminals might keep his aggressive mouth shut for some time.</Text>
      </Text>
      <Text>
        <GUID>1414040611</GUID>
        <Text>Wanted Criminals</Text>
      </Text>
      <Text>
        <GUID>1414040610</GUID>
        <Text>The Arrest Warrant</Text>
      </Text>
      <Text>
        <GUID>1414006768</GUID>
        <Text>At a routine patrol on departures at Majipun harbor, my men have uncovered some irregularities. It would seem that wanted criminals have been able to set sail for your lands. By the Name of the Ruize Emperor, I have an arrest warrant for their immediate detainment. I trust that you will turn them over to me.</Text>
      </Text>
      <Text>
        <GUID>1414006769</GUID>
        <Text>Sake is a religious necessity but by no means a replacement for water. Your people should put some restraint on their consumption.</Text>
      </Text>
      <Text>
        <GUID>1414006771</GUID>
        <Text>Ever since you settled on these islands, people on Majipun are drunk all day! Your inhabitants are making for an appalling example.</Text>
      </Text>
      <Text>
        <GUID>1414006770</GUID>
        <Text>Sustain across the region:&lt;br/&gt; Max. [Conditions QuestCondition Amount]% of [AssetData([Conditions QuestCondition Context]) Text] supply for [Conditions QuestCondition TimeLimit &gt;&gt; time] (Current: [Conditions QuestCondition CurrentAmount]%)</Text>
      </Text>
      <Text>
        <GUID>1414040616</GUID>
        <Text>Recollection</Text>
      </Text>
      <Text>
        <GUID>1414006744</GUID>
        <Text>Trader Good</Text>
      </Text>
      <Text>
        <GUID>1414006745</GUID>
        <Text>These unique beasts are found only within the untouched karsts in the southern provinces of the Tianming Empire. With humans slowly taking over these secluded bamboo forests, these rare animals might soon find themselves at risk of displacement, or even worse.</Text>
      </Text>
      <Text>
        <GUID>1414006027</GUID>
        <Text>48 hours? Ivy, turn off the game now!</Text>
      </Text>
    </ModOp>
</ModOps>