<ModOps>
  <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414015081</GUID>
      <Text>Rice Warehouse</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414006474</GUID>
      <Text>Doubles within the blink of an eye.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>14740110</GUID>
      <Text>Blockade Runner: Drugs</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414006575</GUID>
      <Text>Tantive</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>14740110</GUID>
      <Text>Blockade Runner (Drugs)</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>14740120</GUID>
      <Text>Blockade Runner (Valuables)</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>14740121</GUID>
      <Text>Blockade Runner (Alcohol)</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>14740122</GUID>
      <Text>Blockade Runner (Luxuries)</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>14740123</GUID>
      <Text>Blockade Runner (Weapons)</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>14740124</GUID>
      <Text>Blockade Runner</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>14740105</GUID>
      <Text>Junk</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>14740106</GUID>
      <Text>Junk</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>14740107</GUID>
      <Text>Junk</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>14740111</GUID>
      <Text>Royal Ship-of-the-Line</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>14740112</GUID>
      <Text>Royal Ship-of-the-Line</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>14740113</GUID>
      <Text>Royal Ship-of-the-Line</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414006593</GUID>
      <Text>Bonus Residents from:</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414006643</GUID>
      <Text>Import Goods</Text>
    </Text>
    <!-- Cookhouse Fluffs -->
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414006691</GUID>
      <Text>The Nóngmín find great pleasure in traditional cooking.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414006692</GUID>
      <Text>Oshizushi, or pressed sushi, is a traditional delicacy crafted in cookhouses where layers of vinegared rice and cured fish are carefully pressed into wooden molds. Originally developed as a method of preservation, this culinary rootstock has since developed into the many other forms of sushi known today.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414006693</GUID>
      <Text>Soy sauce is a fermented seasoning brewed in cookhouses through a careful balance of soybeans, wheat, salt, and time, resulting in a rich, savory liquid. Once a method of preserving soybeans, it has become an essential ingredient known for its deep umami flavor and versatile use in countless dishes.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414006835</GUID>
      <Text>Noodles are handcrafted strands of dough prepared in cookhouses by stretching, cutting, or rolling wheat or rice flour into delicate forms. Once a simple staple, they’ve evolved into a versatile base for hearty broths, stir-fries, and countless regional specialties.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414006837</GUID>
      <Text>Tofu, prized for its subtle taste and adaptability, is made in cookhouses by curdling fresh soy milk and pressing it into blocks. Originating as a simple meat alternative, it has become a culinary canvas, absorbing the essence of broths, sauces, and seasonings.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414006780</GUID>
      <Text>Roast duck is marinated with fragrant spices and slowly roasted to achieve a crisp, golden skin and tender, flavorful meat. This time-honored technique transforms a humble ingredient into a richly seasoned centerpiece of the table.</Text>
    </Text>
    <!-- Influence Category -->
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414018315</GUID>
      <Text>Magnate/Investor Houses</Text>
    </Text>
    <!-- Garden Ornament Fluffs -->
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414018316</GUID>
      <Text>Stepping on this is regarded a criminal offense.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414018317</GUID>
      <Text>Strengthens the community spirit.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414018318</GUID>
      <Text>Perfectly balanced, as all things should be.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414018319</GUID>
      <Text>The bushes are cut exactly as circular as the raked circle around them.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414018320</GUID>
      <Text>It’s “the floor is lava,” only that the lava’s cooled off.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414018321</GUID>
      <Text>A continuous gravel surface that doesn't really look like a continuous gravel surface.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414018322</GUID>
      <Text>Planted islands within a wide sea of gravel.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414018323</GUID>
      <Text>Small rock islands within a wide sea of gravel.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414018324</GUID>
      <Text>The arrangement of the gravel symbolizes the flow of the water.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414018325</GUID>
      <Text>Provides walking space to visiting observers.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414018326</GUID>
      <Text>The number of roofs is uneven, as it always was.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414018327</GUID>
      <Text>Seperates your Garden into tableaus, so observers can never see the full picture, just impressions.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414018328</GUID>
      <Text>Walking through this gate often feels like entering a different dimension.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414018329</GUID>
      <Text>A single tree amidst dry stone paving.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414018330</GUID>
      <Text>Uncut trees, untouched nature within untouched nature.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414018331</GUID>
      <Text>A decoratory statue.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414018332</GUID>
      <Text>Provides much needed light at night.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414018333</GUID>
      <Text>A pillar carved from a single stone block</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414018334</GUID>
      <Text>This is the way.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414018335</GUID>
      <Text>Many centuries ago, these dragon-headed gates were built for high officials.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414018336</GUID>
      <Text>A tall, graceful grass with silken plumes that sway in the wind — capable of transforming land into a silver sea.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414018337</GUID>
      <Text>Good neighborhoods are built on good fences.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414018338</GUID>
      <Text>No one intends to build a wall.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414018339</GUID>
      <Text>An entry with grandeur.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414018340</GUID>
      <Text>The dry rocks form a natural sculpture.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414018341</GUID>
      <Text>Vegetation near ground.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414018342</GUID>
      <Text>A graceful frame draped in cascading wisteria blooms, filling the air with a sweet fragrance above your head.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414018343</GUID>
      <Text>Flying high, a koi swimming in the wind — and yet forever tethered to the earth.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414018344</GUID>
      <Text>The dry dragon resides in the dry water.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414018345</GUID>
      <Text>A miniature one-story pagoda for bells to make loud noises in.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1441400</GUID>
      <Text>Orchard (Horai)</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414042800</GUID>
      <Text>The Shipwreck</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414042801</GUID>
      <Text>Suspicious Crates</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414042803</GUID>
      <Text>I have an assignment for you: I have — no — had a perfectly legal ship that has floundered in a storm. I hear you have a salvager on hand. Would you be able to recover the cargo from the wreck and return it to me? As quietly as possible, of course.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414042804</GUID>
      <Text>Goodwill approaches quickly, looking very frightened. He claims to have a "perfectly legal" ship that, by some unfortunate accident, struck a reef and sank nearby during a storm. With urgency, requests your assistance in discreetly salvaging the ship's cargo.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414042805</GUID>
      <Text>I know you're aiding that cursed smuggler! That wealth rightfully belongs to the great Ruize Emperor, and I will reclaim it shortly!</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1441403</GUID>
      <Text>Import Pier: Noble Mushroom</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414018346</GUID>
      <Text>Caviar made from herring roe offers a briny, delicate flavor with a firm texture, echoing the elegance of its traditional counterpart. Though crafted from humble origins, it carries the same spirit of indulgence and careful preparation.</Text>
    </Text>
    <!-- ETA Export Quests -->
     
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414045000</GUID>
      <Text>E.T.A. Delivery: Bow vs. Arrow</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414045002</GUID>
      <Text>[AssetData([NotificationContext CharacterGUID]) Text] sweatingly thanks you for returning the remains of the Pirates.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414045013</GUID>
      <Text>[AssetData([NotificationContext CharacterGUID]) Text] wants to give you the Arrow Howitzer</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414045003</GUID>
      <Text>Howitzer "Arrow"</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414045004</GUID>
      <Text>Remains</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414045005</GUID>
      <Text>Nearly unidentifiable pirate remains.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414045006</GUID>
      <Text>A 24 cm heavy howitzer, powerful enaugh to turn any pirate ship into a wreckage in a single shot.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414045006</GUID>
      <Text>A 24 cm heavy howitzer, powerful enaugh to turn any pirate ship into a wreckage in a single shot.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414045006</GUID>
      <Text>Have in Horai: &lt;br/&gt;[Conditions QuestCondition CurrentAmount]/[Conditions QuestCondition Amount] [AssetData([Conditions QuestCondition Context]) Text]</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414045008</GUID>
      <Text>I only wish the Queen’s Jumping Jack Blake could restrain himself the way Tianming mandarins do... Oh, what our beloved throne has come to! Regardless, with the admiral silenced for the next few weeks, I can finally start selling our stock — there shouldn’t be any further disturbances.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414045009</GUID>
      <Text>It seems those madmen are pressing ahead with their scheme after all. The desk jockeys back in the Royal Council won’t sanction another round of directly agressive negotiations with the Admiral. So if he and his petty pirate venture insist on the hard way, so be it. There’ll be no official court case — their charred remains will serve as the only verdict.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414045010</GUID>
      <Text>I have credible intelligence that pirates are regrouping in a nearby bay, with the intent of sinking our shipment if they catch sight of it. Naturally, the Throne will deny any involvement, as they always do. Bloodshed can be avoided — provided we maintain sufficient deterrence.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414045011</GUID>
      <Text>The Treaty of Equality explicitly allows for an unlimited export of alcohol into the Tianming Empire. For a shipment of this size, the Admiral may need a gentle reminder of that fact.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414045012</GUID>
      <Text>Use [AssetData(1414045003) Text] on:&lt;br/&gt;[AssetData([Conditions QuestCondition Context]) Text] [Conditions QuestCondition CurrentAmount]/[Conditions QuestCondition Amount]</Text>
    </Text>
    <!-- Agricultral Literature Quest -->
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414041900</GUID>
      <Text>Agricultural Literature</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414041901</GUID>
      <Text>A Gōngrén approaches you, requesting your help in organizing his late father's legacy into a specialized treatise on agriculture, to ensure that his father's hard-earned knowledge can continue to educate others.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414041902</GUID>
      <Text>My father, an honorable agronomist, has sadly passed away. I wish to preserve his wisdom by gathering it into a book, so that his knowledge may live on. Will you help me?</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414041903</GUID>
      <Text>Please deliver this manuscript to the Admiral. I trust he can share its knowledge across the nation. With hope, it will help many more people lead better lives.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414041904</GUID>
      <Text>An unassuming paperback, containing a lifetime of agricultural research from every corner of the Tianming Empire.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <!-- QuestItem -->
      <GUID>1414041905</GUID>
      <Text>Agricultural Literature Manuscript</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414041906</GUID>
      <Text>What? Mr. Yuan has passed away? I see. His work was held in high esteem among my peers and the literati. We must ensure this knowledge is shared — building a pagoda in his honor would be a fitting tribute."</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414041907</GUID>
      <Text>Rest in peace, Father. Your wisdom will endure, and one day, our lands will know no hunger.</Text>
    </Text>
    <!-- Hideaway (Val02) -->
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414045100</GUID>
      <Text>E.T.A. Delivery: Hideaway</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414045101</GUID>
      <Text>Nearly everyone has heard the tales of pirates burying treasure on distant islands. For some, these stories evoke fond memories of childhood adventures. For others, they serve as a clever inspiration for bypassing customs controls.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414045102</GUID>
      <Text>Choose an export location to bring the Valuables to.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414045103</GUID>
      <Text>No, I don't believe that this island is suitable. No cave, no hideaway.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414045104</GUID>
      <Text>I have a feeling this island might already be claimed. Just leave him where he is — he’s obnoxiously talented at music.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414045105</GUID>
      <Text>Let me &lt;br/&gt;Feel the sky and feel the moon &lt;br/&gt;Let me sing an honest tune &lt;br/&gt;To my hideaway</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414045106</GUID>
      <Text>Yes, this is it. We can stash the supply chests in the caves, and the customer will take it from there.</Text>
    </Text>
    <!-- Sunken Not-So-Treasures (Drg01) -->     
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414042400</GUID>
      <Text>E.T.A. Delivery: Sunken Not-So-Treasures</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414042401</GUID>
      <Text>The Admiral is actively blocking the drug imports to Majipun, deliberately violating the Treaty of Equality — and James Goodwill is far too clever to simply let it slide.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414042402</GUID>
      <Text>Roughly calculating the ocean currents and wind patterns, we can predict where we need to drop these buoys so they drift directly ashore on Majpun. Our contacts on the island will then retrieve them.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414042403</GUID>
      <Text>Throw drug buoys exactly onto the markers.</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414042404</GUID>
      <Text>Drug Buoy</Text>
    </Text>
    <!-- Double Agent -->     
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414041700</GUID>
      <Text>Double Agent</Text>
    </Text>   
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414041701</GUID>
      <Text>Admiral Wu knows the Tianming Empire's technology has lagged behind its peers. If he is to repel the invaders tomorrow, he must learn from them today. And so, he has sought you out — will you aid him and fulfill his request?</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414041702</GUID>
      <Text>I know you own many ships, and I wish to take a closer look at them. Could you perhaps share some photos of your fleet?</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414041703</GUID>
      <Text>How wonderful is a ship unbound by the whims of the wind, unlike the junks of our Empire. As we lack the means to produce modern steamships ourselves, I wish to purchase a fleet, which which would significantly enhance trade throughout the region.
</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414041704</GUID>
      <Text>The Ruize Emperor would like to establish the first steam shipyards at Foocheng in the future, and we are currently constructing a prototype trade vessel as part of this initiative. Would a technology transfer of steam turbines be possible? Unfortunately our engineers are unfamiliar with steam engines of this complexity...</Text>
    </Text>
    <!-- The Revolt -->     
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414041100</GUID>
      <Text>The Revolt</Text>
    </Text>   
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414041101</GUID>
      <Text>A mysterious stranger from the Old World has been stirring unrest among the Gōngrén at a local factory. The Magnate requests that you investigate the matter further.</Text>
    </Text>   
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414041102</GUID>
      <Text>This individual has been giving me plenty of headaches recently. He claims to speak for the people, but pah! He's only here to sow chaos. He mentioned some doctor in the Old World, but I highly doubt any reputable doctor would associate with such an imbecile. Property in the hands of ordinary people? Ridiculous! It's nothing but a farce. You must stop him by any means necessary!</Text>
    </Text>   
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414041103</GUID>
      <Text>Finally, this fool's been arrested. But it seems his capture has stirred the workers so greatly that they refuse to work without him. They've gone on strike, demanding his return. You need to act quickly! I can't afford to lose any more profits. Pay his caution, and get him out of these lands, where he can't cause anymore trouble!</Text>
    </Text>   
    <!-- River Rebellion (Wpn02) -->
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414047000</GUID>
      <Text>E.T.A. Delivery: River Rebellion</Text>
    </Text>   
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414047001</GUID>
      <Text>A rebellion in the Tianming mainlands is rapidly escalating. Soon, more weapons will be required, as insurgent farmers prepare to launch an attack on the Imperial Capital.</Text>
    </Text>   
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414047002</GUID>
      <Text>Internal matters of the Tianming Empire usually do not interest us, provided they hold up the treaties they signed. Yet it is clear that the moment the opportunity arises, they will seek to breach these agreements. With this in mind, it is in our best interest to back the growing rebellion now poised to strike at their capital. We shall send these weapons up the Huanghe River and, without interference, allow the rebels to seize the ships.</Text>
    </Text>   
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414047003</GUID>
      <Text>This is enough. With these photographs, the rebels will be able to identify the ships carrying their weapons. They've already sent one of their spies to collect the photographs.</Text>
    </Text>   
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414047004</GUID>
      <Text>Rebel Friend</Text>
    </Text>   
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414047005</GUID>
      <Text>Photograph of Civilian Vessels</Text>
    </Text>   
    <!-- Freeport (Lux02) -->
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414047100</GUID>
      <Text>E.T.A. Delivery: Freeport</Text>
    </Text>   
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414047101</GUID>
      <Text>Goodwill has secured a buyer for your entire stock of Luxuries. Moving the shipment through customs is a breeze, as foreign trading companies conveniently feature tax-exempt spaces.</Text>
    </Text>   
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414047102</GUID>
      <Text>My client has requested that we deliver his shipment directly to the trading company to the highway robbery that is the tax office. From there, we can deposit it into his freeport storage, allowing him to store the goods indefinitely without ever paying taxes or customs fees.</Text>
    </Text>   
    <!-- Eastern Medicine -->
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414042900</GUID>
      <Text>Eastern Medicine</Text>
  </Text>        
  <Text>
      <GUID>1414042901</GUID>
      <Text>A young local doctor, curious about modern Western medicine, dreams of blending it with traditional Eastern medicine. With determination, he knocks on your office door, seeking your guidance and collaboration.</Text>
  </Text> 
  <Text>
      <GUID>1414042902</GUID>
      <Text>Hello Administrator. My family has practiced medicine for generations and yet I've been wondering — could Western and Eastern medicine be combined? First, I'd like to see what a Western hospital is really like.</Text>
  </Text>
  <Text>
      <GUID>1414042903</GUID>
      <Text>Oh, excellent. Next, I'd like to examine some of the medicines used in these hospitals. That should give me some ideas.</Text>
  </Text>
  <!-- Furious Fourier -->
  <Text>
      <GUID>1414041200</GUID>
      <Text>Fourious Fourier</Text>
  </Text>    
  <Text>
      <GUID>1414041201</GUID>
      <Text>The Admiral, disdain for the Old World set aside, remains curious about the technologies of the West, which are said to be more advanced than those in the Tianming Empire.</Text>
  </Text>      
  <Text>
      <GUID>1414041202</GUID>
      <Text>Your engineers’ inventions are remarkable. I have read about these devices, yet I don’t fully understand how these mass-produced "radios" function. How is it that one's voice can be captured and transmitted through a crystal?</Text>
  </Text>         
  <Text>
      <GUID>1414041203</GUID>
      <Text>Fascinating... Truly fascinating. If you could provide me with a few of these so-called "detectors" capable of transmitting sound, my Emperor would gladly reward such collaboration in the field of signal transmission. In fact, we could offer our inexpensive labor force in return.</Text>
  </Text>        
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414042410</GUID>
      <Text>Fetch [AssetData(1414042404) Text] from:&lt;br/&gt;[AssetData([Conditions QuestCondition ItemPlace]) Text]</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414042411</GUID>
      <Text>[AssetData([NotificationContext CharacterGUID]) Text] wants to give you the Drug Bouys</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>14443032</GUID>
      <Text>All Company Production</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414045111</GUID>
      <Text>Pickup 200t packaged goods at James Goodwills Lighthouse</Text>
    </Text>
    <Text>
      <GUID>1414045108</GUID>
      <Text>Potential Hideaway</Text>
    </Text>
  </ModOp>
</ModOps>
