<ModOps>
    <ModOp Type="add" Path="/TextExport/Texts">
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414041400</GUID>
            <Text>Under Pyrphorian Threat</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414041401</GUID>
            <Text>Several trade ships of mine bound for the Old World have gone missing. My trade partner has written urgently, demanding the goods be delivered without further delay. I need you to investigate the situation immediately.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414041402</GUID>
            <Text>E.T.A. Shipment of Illegal Cargo</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414041403</GUID>
            <Text>E.T.A. Transporter Wreckage</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414041404</GUID>
            <Text>"What? The Pyrphorians? That can’t be right… they never stray this far from their base. It seems we'll need to calculate a new route. Thank you for saving my cargo. Would you be willing to escort our next trade run? We're short on protection these days — escorts just aren’t keeping up."</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414041405</GUID>
            <Text>Thank you so much. We were on our way to the Old World to meet a trade partner when we were ambushed by a Pyrophorian patrol. They don’t usually venture this far out..."</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414041406</GUID>
            <Text>A trade ship fleet belonging to James Goodwill seems to have gone missing. He wants you to investigate further.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414042201</GUID>
            <Text>[AssetData([NotificationContext CharacterGUID]) Text] offers accepting your specialist as a tribute.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414042206</GUID>
            <Text>[AssetData([NotificationContext CharacterGUID]) Text] grants you protection for the tribute</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414042207</GUID>
            <Text>Protection from Pyrphorians I</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414042208</GUID>
            <Text>You have brought the Pyrphorians a tribute for their sacrifices. In exchange, they have granted you a limited-time security guarantee.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414042209</GUID>
            <Text>Protection from Pyrphorians II</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414042210</GUID>
            <Text>Protection from Pyrphorians III</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414042211</GUID>
            <Text>Protection from Pyrphorians IV</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414042212</GUID>
            <Text>Protection from Pyrphorians V</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414041501</GUID>
            <Text>The Gōngrén laboring in one of the Magnate's numerous factories are demanding improved working conditions. The Magnate strongly opposes these demands and has requested your assistance in resolving the matter.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414041502</GUID>
            <Text>Give the Magnate a blank check</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414041503</GUID>
            <Text>Hear out the Gōngrén</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414041504</GUID>
            <Text>These workers are lucky to have jobs at all, yet now they’re demanding better conditions? Preposterous! Their actions are jeopardizing the efficiency of my factories, and I need this dealt with swiftly. Speak to them if you must, but don't waste my time.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414041505</GUID>
            <Text>You're already working us to death! Our breaks are only 30 minutes a day, and if we're even a few minutes late, we're locked out for the rest of the day. A friend of mine lost his hand in a machine accident, but when an inspector came, he claimed everything was 'safe.' My friend didn't even get a single day off to recover, and when he couldn’t work the next day, he was fired. He still hasn't been able to find another job. Please, we're desperate — we beg you to help us!</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414041506</GUID>
            <Text>Side with the Magnate</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414041507</GUID>
            <Text>Side with the Gōngrén</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414041508</GUID>
            <Text>"The Magnate is right. They should be grateful to have work. You've done nothing wrong. The factory can run just fine as it is."</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414041509</GUID>
            <Text>"A single human life is worth more than all the profits this Magnate amasses. I will ensure this matter is resolved — and the factories held fully accountable."</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414041510</GUID>
            <Text>Mediate between the Magnate and his workers</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414041500</GUID>
            <Text>Unfair! But for whom?</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414041512</GUID>
            <Text>[AssetData([NotificationContext CharacterGUID]) Text] offers you a decision quest</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414041514</GUID>
            <Text>"We must all tighten our belts"</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414041516</GUID>
            <Text>"We must all tighten our belts"</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414041515</GUID>
            <Text>Solidarity with the common worker</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414041517</GUID>
            <Text>Solidarity with the common worker</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414041518</GUID>
            <Text>Promise to discuss a bill on this in a future Parliament hearing.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414043000</GUID>
            <Text>Exotic food</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414043001</GUID>
            <Text>"The owner of a streetfood stall has noticed a steady decline in business. In hopes of spicing things up, he wishes to try out some foreign cuisines in order to develop new recipes. Will you lend a hand in his culinary quest?</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414043002</GUID>
            <Text>Business has been slow... I'm afraid I might lose my food stall. Maybe something exotic could turn things around. Could you bring me some unusual dishes? Something that might spark a little inspiration.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414042500</GUID>
            <Text>The Management Experiment</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414042501</GUID>
            <Text>A wealthy magnate has approached you with a bold proposal: to oversee a cross-generational management experiment in radio manufacturing, designed to test the validity of his latest management theory.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414042502</GUID>
            <Text>Salutations! I am Docteur Tzeentch, Head of Imperial Management at the Royal Bourse. With your leave, I wish to validate my latest theory in practical governance — on one of your islands, of course.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414042503</GUID>
            <Text>Yes, yes — this is a positive outcome. It is evident that the supposition advanced is indeed valid. The next step is to verify the extension equation.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414042504</GUID>
            <Text>Sustain:&lt;br/&gt;Increased productivity from working conditions in [AssetData(1441015) Text]: [Conditions QuestCondition CurrentAmount]/[Conditions QuestCondition Amount]% for [Conditions QuestCondition TimeLimit &gt;&gt; time]</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414042505</GUID>
            <Text>Enough is enough! These bloody experiments are unbearable! We quit!</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414043400</GUID>
            <Text>If it Looks Like a Duck...</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414043401</GUID>
            <Text>A magnate has approached you with an unusual request. His young daughter has recently developed an intense fascination with ducks and has been endlessly pestering him about them. A photo of a few ducks, just for her, might help soothe the irate three-year-old.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414043402</GUID>
            <Text>You have to help me. My daughter is three years old and has suddenly decided that ducks are the greatest thing in the world. Morning to night, it’s on and on about those silly birds. I can’t sleep. I can’t think. Please — just bring me a photograph of some ducks. Maybe it’ll buy me a moment of peace.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414043600</GUID>
            <Text>An Innocent Interest</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414043601</GUID>
            <Text>Goodwill has enlisted your help for a rather vague contract, claiming it involves advancing the collective expertise of the oil industry. It's probably all above-board... probably.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414043602</GUID>
            <Text>My good friend! Always reliable, always discreet. It has come to my attention that certain... technical flourishes in the design of your oil derricks have caught the eye of a few industry insiders in the Royal Council. They’re eager to know more — and they’re willing to pay handsomely for it!</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414043500</GUID>
            <Text>Ungracious Guests</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414043501</GUID>
            <Text>A military courier serving Admiral Wu made a brief stop at a Gōngrén's home during his journey, only for the troops to eat all of the host's food. Help replenish what was lost.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414043502</GUID>
            <Text>Typical! Some imperious little officer under Wu’s flag had to halt for the night while on his way to deliver reports or some nonsense. But by morning, I discovered that he and his band of no-good troops had emptied every jar and shelf in my kitchen! They devoured all my food, the nerve! Can you help me replace what they took?</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414042600</GUID>
            <Text>The Imperial Envoy</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414042601</GUID>
            <Text>You have been approached by Admiral Wu, who is seeking your help in combating local pirates. He insists it's to impress the forthcoming imperial envoy and showcase his success. Yet, something about the situation feels off — it seems that things are not that simple...</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414042602</GUID>
            <Text>The Emperor's envoy, General Li — my old friend and foe — is set to inspect the progress in Horai. Move quickly! There's work to be done!</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414042603</GUID>
            <Text>Excellent! These shipwrecks are a testament to the success of my work here! Next, we’ll meet General Li briefly before his departure. Wait! Where is he slipping off to? Follow him!</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414042607</GUID>
            <Text>Pyrphorian Cruiser</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414042606</GUID>
            <Text>General Li's Trustworthy Junk</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414042604</GUID>
            <Text>Pirate Junk</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414042608</GUID>
            <Text>Why? ... Him too?! ... A traitor! ... Yes! We must find such proof! </Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414042609</GUID>
            <Text>Take a photo of General Li's meeting with the Pyrphorians as proof.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414042610</GUID>
            <Text>These are your rewards. I'm certain you're smart enough to remain silent until I make my report. Our Imperial authorities have no ties to these arsonists! This is all the work of that cursed traitor!</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414042700</GUID>
            <Text>The Emperor's Birthday</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414042701</GUID>
            <Text>The birthday of the Emperor of the Tianming Empire is fast approaching. Admiral Wu, wishing to present something unique to the Emperor, has approached you with a request to acquire one of your exotic artworks.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414042702</GUID>
            <Text>His Celestial Majesty, the Ruize Emperor, approaches his birthday with great anticipation. It is the duty and honour of a loyal servant like myself to present His Majesty with gifts fit for his greatness. I know His Majesty has a deep fondness for rare and exotic artwork from distant lands. You must supply me with the finest pieces. But remember, only the best will do!</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414042703</GUID>
            <Text>Bring a legendary artifact to Admiral Wu.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414042704</GUID>
            <Text>This artwork is truly magnificent. I will send it to the Imperial Palace immediately... wait... it appears pirates have set their sights on my birthday gift for the Emperor! There's no time to waste — destroy them and save the masterpiece!</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414042705</GUID>
            <Text>Excellent! For security reasons, your payment will be settled after you have escorted the convoy carrying the Emperor's birthday gifts to safety. I assure you, the reward will be doubled for this task.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414042706</GUID>
            <Text>The Emperor's Birthday Gifts</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414042707</GUID>
            <Text>Transporter with Gifts</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414042708</GUID>
            <Text>Escort the Emperor's Birthday Gifts out of the region.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414042709</GUID>
            <Text>Pirate Junk</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414042710</GUID>
            <Text>A collection of gifts assembled by the Admiral.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414042712</GUID>
            <Text>Select the Transporter waiting with the gifts.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414043700</GUID>
            <Text>To Build Better</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414043701</GUID>
            <Text>The people of Majipun seek samples of cement from the Old World to compare with their own local materials.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414043702</GUID>
            <Text>Though our sanhetu concrete is of the highest quality, some scholars within the Tiangming Guo are eager to study the properties of the limestone used in your own cement. It just so happens I have been tasked to facilitate this, and so you can bring the materials directly to me.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414043800</GUID>
            <Text>Portraiture Most Luminous</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414043801</GUID>
            <Text>Lithophanes are a quickly growing fancy among your Magnates. There's money to be made here.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414043802</GUID>
            <Text>Have you lately seen those exquisite porcelain backplates everyone’s been displaying in their second parlors? I'm sponsoring a venture to manufacture them here. Bring me the materials, and you'll have your share of the profits.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414043300</GUID>
            <Text>Selective Breeding</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414043301</GUID>
            <Text>A group of farmers is experimenting with selective rice breeding to improve yields and enhance resistance to drought, monsoons, pests, and vermin.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414043302</GUID>
            <Text>The rice in our fields grows taller than humans. When I lie down dreaming among the stalks, their heavy golden ears shield me from the sun.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414043303</GUID>
            <Text>These make for a promising start for experimentation. Now, we need resilient crops from the far side of the world — ones that can withstand disease. We will cross them with our rice plants and strengthen our yields. Our harvests and those of our children must be secured at all cost!</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414043200</GUID>
            <Text>The Radio Management</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414043201</GUID>
            <Text>A wealthy magnate proposes building a radio tower on the island where he lives, offering to fund its construction and hire scholars to operate it. In return, he believes he should have unrestricted access to its use. The scholars, however, argue that in the spirit of progress, at a few of the channels should be reserved for scientific research and discovery. Whose vision will you support?</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414043202</GUID>
            <Text>I've put together a comprehensive business plan for investing in public radio infrastructure. What’s that noise out there — regulation??? Pff... Build that tower, I’ll have the check signed before they even lodging the first complaint.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414043204</GUID>
            <Text>"All radio frequencies should be subject to the rules of the free market! Those protestors are so entitled that they actually believe some channels should be reserved for scientific research and not advertising, which is directly contradicts the deal!</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414043205</GUID>
            <Text>Mediate a Deal</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414043206</GUID>
            <Text>Subject all frequencies to the free market</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414043207</GUID>
            <Text>Protect some frequencies for scientific research</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414043208</GUID>
            <Text>Celebrate the deal with a party</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414043209</GUID>
            <Text>Quietly sign the deal</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414043210</GUID>
            <Text>Well done! I knew you'd never pass up a deal like that. Congratulations — you’re officially one of us now! Let’s raise a toast to our new asset, made possible by private capital, all for the wellbeing of everyone!</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414043211</GUID>
            <Text>Private Funding</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414043212</GUID>
            <Text>We won't even realize that the Magnates have placed themselves between us and our public services until it's too late.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414043213</GUID>
            <Text>IETE Fellowship</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414043214</GUID>
            <Text>For science! Now, while we’re on the subject of wise investments, could you kindly provide us with the necessary experimental instruments? We must begin our research at once!</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414043215</GUID>
            <Text>In recognition of your outstanding contributions, we are pleased to invite you to join us as an Honorary Fellow of the Institute of Electrical and Telegraphic Engineers for the upcoming summit!</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414043216</GUID>
            <Text>Continue</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414043217</GUID>
            <Text>Deliver a boring speech about how it is absolutely essential for everyone else to invest in research.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414043218</GUID>
            <Text>Money and standardization make research easier.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414043219</GUID>
            <Text>Make the investment</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414043904</GUID>
            <Text>ANNOnymous</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414043902</GUID>
            <Text>Goodwill's Customer</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414043903</GUID>
            <Text>E.T.A. Freighter</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414043900</GUID>
            <Text>E.T.A. Delivery: Prime Shipping</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1440508</GUID>
            <Text>Packaged Goods</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414043905</GUID>
            <Text>My men have loaded the contraband onto the transporters. Our client prefers to distribute the risk for his own safety, so he’s provided us with four rendezvous points. However, our schedule is tight — this delivery must be completed without delay!</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414044006</GUID>
            <Text>Our customers have requested delivery by airdrop, and the E.T.A. always delivers what the customer orders. Unfortunately, Omega Haven doesn’t have an airship dock for your fleet, so the only option is to load it onto our own airship in the hangar. I want that back in one piece — and don’t mess up the airdrop!</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414044007</GUID>
            <Text>Deliver your goods by airdrop. Beware: You only have one shot at this!</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414044000</GUID>
            <Text>E.T.A. Delivery: Airlift</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414044009</GUID>
            <Text>Airdrop Location</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414044011</GUID>
            <Text>Tantive</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414044001</GUID>
            <Text>James Goodwill's Airship</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1440509</GUID>
            <Text>Airdrop Contraband</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414044100</GUID>
            <Text>E.T.A. Delivery: Prime Shipping</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414044200</GUID>
            <Text>E.T.A. Delivery: Prime Shipping</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414044300</GUID>
            <Text>E.T.A. Delivery: Prime Shipping</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414044400</GUID>
            <Text>E.T.A. Delivery: Prime Shipping</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414043100</GUID>
            <Text>The Firework Master</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414043104</GUID>
            <Text>A young local Gōngrén arrives at your office, visibly distressed. His parents have been shipwrecked while traveling to visit him, and he pleads for your assistance in rescuing them. In return, he offers the renowned skills of his family to create one of the finest props you’ll ever see for a fireworks display.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414043105</GUID>
            <Text>"Administrator, forgive the intrusion — but there’s been an accident on a ship my family is supposed to be on. I beg you, please… bring them home safely!"</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414043106</GUID>
            <Text>You have our deepest gratitude. My family has crafted fireworks for generations. If you can provide us with some supplies, we would be honored to create a spectacular display in honor of you, as a gift.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414043107</GUID>
            <Text>Very good! I’ll start working on it. Once I’m done, please ensure they don’t end up swimming for their lives again — the this region has already proven treacherous.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414044600</GUID>
            <Text>Tutorial - Wonders</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414044602</GUID>
            <Text>These ruins were once magnificent wonders that towered above the ancient cities of Horai. Now, it’s up to you: clear away the burden of time and uncover the secrets of the lost wonder, or perhaps raise a new marvel in its place. But first things first — time to start with a good spring cleaning!</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414044604</GUID>
            <Text>Now, what magnificence have you uncovered here? As with much of cultural heritage, its meaning is open to interpretation — which means you get to choose which Wonder to rebuild upon these ancient ruins. Keep digging to unlock more Wonders, all of which you'll find in your Construction Menu. But remember: before you can place your chosen Wonder, you'll need to finish the foundation first!</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414044605</GUID>
            <Text>Congratulations, your Wonder Foundation is complete! Now, it’s time to decide what to rebuild here. Browse the Construction Menu, select a Wonder that sparks your interest, and place it in this slot.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414044900</GUID>
            <Text>E.T.A. Delivery: Needle in the Haystack</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414044901</GUID>
            <Text>The Tianming Empire has become a haven for corruption. In fact, gaining the favor of its bureaucrats often requires nothing more than offering a bribe that surpasses what their current superior pays them.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414044902</GUID>
            <Text>Tianming officials have seized all the cargo, just as expected. A few years ago, they would have burned it all on the spot without hesitation. Thankfully, such actions are no longer possible without violating the Treaty of Equality. Now, it will languish and rot in their storage, unless...</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414044903</GUID>
            <Text>Let’s ensure our mole has a busy warehouse, filled with constant cargo transfers to hide in. It would be a shame if all that cargo went to waste. After all, if you were hiding a needle, wouldn't a haystack be the perfect place?</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414044904</GUID>
            <Text>Very well, thank you for being so generous. I will proceed with the deliveries right away.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414044906</GUID>
            <Text>Let your Transporters be caught be Admiral Wu's patrolling ships</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414044907</GUID>
            <Text>Now, what do you say to that? Tianming officials are resuming patrols around Majipun — contrary to all contracts. I'd rather not provoke another Arrow Incident, so how about a little charade instead? Why risk a blockade run when we can trick the blockaders into delivering the goods for us?</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414044908</GUID>
            <Text>Bribe the official at the Warehouse on Majipun</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414044909</GUID>
            <Text>The Official thanks you for the Bribe.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414015081</GUID>
            <Text>Majipun Warehouse</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414044910</GUID>
            <Text>[AssetData([NotificationContext CharacterGUID]) Text] is outraged at your shameless blockade running attempt.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414044912</GUID>
            <Text>The official is ready to take your bribe.</Text>
        </Text>
        <Text>
            <GUID>1414044913</GUID>
            <Text>Sell to Admiral Wu a total of &lt;br/&gt;[Conditions QuestCondition CurrentAmount]/[Conditions QuestCondition Amount] of goods.</Text>
        </Text>
    </ModOp>
</ModOps>